Everyone needs a friend.
Greta is a mystery, thriller, drama film directed by Neil Jordan.
A young woman returns a lonely widow’s lost purse, leading to an unlikely relationship between the
two — until the young woman discovers the widow might not be all that she seems.
Frances McCullen, played by Chloë Grace Moretz.
Greta Hideg, played by Isabelle Huppert.
Erica Penn, played by Maika Monroe.
Chris McCullen, played by Colm Feore.
Brian Cody, played by Stephen Rea.
Alexa Hammond, played by Zawe Ashton.
Greta is a 2018 psychological thriller film directed by Neil
Jordan and written by Ray Wright and Jordan.
The film is an international co-production
between the United States and Ireland.
The film stars Isabelle Huppert, Chloë Grace Moretz, Maika Monroe, Colm Feore and Stephen Rea, and follows
a young woman as she befriends a lonely widow who becomes disturbingly obsessed with her.
Greta held its world premiere at the Toronto
International Film Festival on 6 September 2018.
It was theatrically released on 1 March 2019 in the
United States, by Focus Features.
The film grossed over $18 million worldwide and
received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of new york city, paris,
france, psychopath, finger, stalker.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.